It's the year 2022. People are still the same. They'll do anything
to get what they need. And they need Soylent Green.
Soylent Green is a science fiction, thriller, crime
film directed by Richard Fleischer.
In the year 2022, overcrowding, pollution,  and resource depletion have
reduced society’s leaders to finding food for the teeming masses.
The answer is Soylent Green.
Detective Robert Thorn, played by Charlton Heston.
Shirl, played by Leigh Taylor-Young.
Tab Fielding, played by Chuck Connors.
William R. Simonson, played by Joseph Cotten.
Chief Hatcher, played by Brock Peters.
Martha Phillips, played by Paula Kelly.
Soylent Green is a 1973 American dystopian thriller film directed by Richard
Fleischer, and starring Charlton Heston, Leigh Taylor-Young, and Edward G.
Robinson in his final film role.
It is loosely based on the 1966 science-fiction novel Make Room!
by Harry Harrison, with a plot that combines elements of
science fiction and a police procedural.
The story follows a murder investigation in a dystopian future of dying oceans and year-round humidity caused by the
greenhouse effect, with the resulting pollution, depleted resources, poverty, and overpopulation.
The film was released on April 19, 1973, by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, and received mostly
favorable reviews from critics, while earning $3.6 million at the box office.
In 1973, it won the Nebula Award for Best Dramatic Presentation
and the Saturn Award for Best Science Fiction Film.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, paranoia,
dystopia, greenhouse effect, global warming.
The tone is mind_bending and thought_provoking and intense.